

# **SKILLS**

#### FRONT-END

JavaScript · TypeScript · React · C# · React Native · HTML · CSS · ES6

#### Back-End

NodeJS · Next JS

#### Database

MongoDB · Firebase

#### **Tools and Libraries**

Git · GitHub · ESLint · Jest · Axios ·

Tailwind CSS · Chakra UI · Ant Design ·

GSAP · Sass

### **SOFT SKILLS**

Teamwork · Problem-solving ·

Communication

#### **EDUCATION**

## Alpha JavaScript Track

Telerik Academy

01/2024 - 06/2024

Sofia, Bulgaria

# Bachelor's degree, Accounting

**VUZF** 

10/2009 - 07/2013

Sofia, Bulgaria

Proficient

O

# **LANGUAGES**

Bulgarian Native

**English** 

#### **PASSIONS**

- WEB DEVELOPMENT ENTHUSIAST
- ★ TAKING STROLLS IN NATURE
- BOARD GAMES WITH FRIENDS
- COMPETITIVE GAMING

# RADOSLAV MARINOV

#### JavaScript Developer

- +359888788687 @ radoslav.marinov89@gmail.com
- https://github.com/Radoslav-Marinovv
- Attps://linkedin.com/in/radoslav-marinov-0b940689 Sofia, Bulgaria

## **SUMMARY**

With 1+ year of experience in frontend development and five completed projects, I am a graduate of the Telerik Academy's Alpha JS track. I have developed strong skills in frontend technologies, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, and React, along with back-end knowledge in Node.js, Next.js, and Firebase. I am also well-versed in UI libraries such as Tailwind CSS, Ant Design, and Chakra UI.

I am eager to apply my diverse experience, creative thinking, and technical skills to contribute to the development of software projects and applications.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Portfolio: Portfolio Hosted on Vercel

08/2024 - Present

This portfolio is built with Vite and React and is an ongoing project designed to showcase my skills and experience. It features smooth animations with GSAP and responsive design using Tailwind CSS. Through this platform, I aim to present my personal projects, technical abilities, and creativity.

- React.js, Type Script
- TailwindCSS, GSAP, Git

https://radoslav-marinov-portfolio.vercel.app/

## Fitness Tracking Application: Motion Mate

06/2024 - 06/2024

Fitness tracking application, where users can track their daily exercises, such as calories burned, exercises done, or other activities. Users can set their goals and track their progress. They can also add their friends and see their progress as well.

- · React.js, JavaScript, Firebase, Tailwind CSS
- · daisy UI, Git

Phttps://a58-agents-team1.github.io/Motion.Mate/

## Forum: Tasty Recipe Talk

05/2024 - 05/2024

As part of a team, I was involved in creating the food recipe forum, creating the database connection, the GitHub repository. Building functionality and style of the project.

- React.js, JavaScript, Firebase
- Chakra Ul. Git

# RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

### Freelance Developer

02/2023 - 06/2023

### **Groshev & Partners**

Sofia, Bulgaria

Led client communication to understand and refine project requirements, planned the optimal technologies for the project, and outlined the steps needed to meet the client's criteria.

- Next.js, React.js, Type Script, JSON
- Additional Libraries: TailwindCSS, Daisy UI, Google Blogger API

#### Frontend Developer

06/2022 - 12/2022

# TECHSTORM LTD

Sofia, Bulgaria

Participating in the creation of an MVP for a website as a frontend developer and a mobile application, extended existing functionality and implemented new features by completing assigned tasks.

- Tech stack: Next.js, React.js, React Native, Type Script, MongoDB, JSON.
- Additional Libraries: Auth0, Ant Design, Axios, Moment JS, TailwindCSS, React Router.